Thank you, Vince.
Pursued from Romdeau by a monster called PROXY,
I managed to escape to the outside world.
After losing everything, only doubt and a single choice remain.
If I go to Mosk, my homeland,
I might be able to figure something out.
The journey thus began,
and several days have passed...
It's not just our bodies that have weakened.
The overcast sky stretches endlessly above.
The frozen ground stretches endlessly below.
Threatening to chill us to the depths of our souls,
the view haunts us.
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
How is she?
Ah yes,
it's only been three days,
but the acclimatization rate of the amrita mimic
cells we are administering is increasing as planned.
With regard to possible complications stemming
from a weakened immune system due to the infection,
there are no problems so far.
At this rate,
we believe we can allow her to
continue treatment at home as early as today.
Then, we will bring her to you at a later time.
The newest data has been uploaded.
This ability to heal...
You surprise me every time,
Re-l...
meditation    re-l 124C41+
Chairman Daedalus.
PROXY has already disappeared from Romdeau's vicinity.
That is a certainty.
If you have any specific information, please disclose-
Do not forget.
While we are individuals, we are also a collective.
If the Research Bureau knows how to track PROXY,
then the Security Bureau's position-
Quarrels between the bureaus are of-
What we sense,
in other words, is that we are capable
of knowing everything about Romdeau.
We are able to verify PROXY's presence just by connecting.
PROXY does not "exist" in Romdeau.
That is the only truth.
Then this individual would like to pose a question to the collective.
What is the significance of we citizens
allowing someone to return from the outside world,
when we have always refused to do so?
You do not have the right to
request disclosure of that information.
It is time.
Knowing the truth
does not necessarily bring happiness.
Actually accepting such an obvious fact of life...
takes such a long time.
I've become painfully aware that it is my weakness.
Grandfather's lie...
A world exists outside this city.
There, people lead their own lives.
I've become aware of this fact.
That is why...
I must not flee from this reality.
Why is that here?
Daedalus,
as I'd suspected, you...
This is the artificial womb.
Daedalus!
This is where all Romdeau citizens are born: the Womb Room.
Daedalus...
Why?
I must insist that you return the tools of my trade.
If even one of these is missing, I won't be able to cover for you.
Well, I must compliment you on your curiosity.
Come with me.
I'll show this to you.
Biologically, and from a structural
standpoint, this life maintenance system
is the most efficient production line possible for the dome.
Here, we are born to become model
citizens and be raised by model citizens.
Everything is managed and restricted;
the balance is maintained.
In order to live in an environment such as the dome,
managing and stabilizing the population is, after all, critical.
Re-l?
I'm fine.
So the creation of humans, like
autoreivs, is controlled by a production line?
Still,
although I can understand that on an intellectual level...
It's a different matter entirely when you actually see it?
Manipulative intrusions into life processes...
By continuing to do so, we are prolonging the human race.
This is reality...?
If so, what was the outside world I saw?
Daedalus, tell me.
Is this dome actually necessary as a system for model citizens?
If an outside world truly exists,
hasn't the system outlived its usefulness already?
I am an idiot...
I almost lost someone dear to me.
I...
should not have let you go outside.
It's too late now.
I can't run from the truth that I've come to know.
Indeed.
The promise...
Do you remember it?
Yes.
But could you at least let me save some face first?
You want me to go see Grandfather?
He's right.
Before I depart on a journey for truth,
there is someone I must face.
A world in which there is neither presence of man
nor any trace of life.
Mosk supposedly lies...
a great distance beyond it.
And...
exhaustion marks every face.
Grandfather,
I am sorry to have caused you worry.
Re-l,
are you satisfied?
What did you see in the outside world?
Feel free to tell us without hesitation.
Have you lost the ability of speech?
There were people.
There was a livelihood.
There was a world.
I see.
Why do you hide this?
Re-l.
What are you afraid of?
You go too far-
I am speaking with my grandfather.
No answers, I see.
I wonder how long it's been
since we left Romdeau behind.
His face shows signs of exhaustion.
And...
yet another falls...
Re-l.
Re-l!
His decisions were deemed inappropriate,
so he'd been sent off for readjustment.
I decided to take him in.
I'll go make some preparations.
If Prince Charming hadn't been around,
I'd be scrap metal by now.
Did you lose some weight?
You look pale, too.
You can't do without me, can you?
Hey, Re-l.
What's with the cold shoulder?
Because you... are still...
Well then.
Now it's time for me to fulfill my promise.
Wait.
Before that...
Ah,
I haven't told you yet, have I.
I made the same modifications to Iggy as my assistants.
You disconnected their link to the surveillance structure.
That's right.
In effect, Iggy's "ears" are no longer your grandfather's.
Now I can badmouth the Security Bureau.
Well then.
On to the main topic:
the autopsy results of the life form
you reported as being brutally killed
in the deepest area of the outer shell...
But before that,
let me tell you everything I know from the very beginning.
An era is ending.
Chief?
The Administrator's decline in health
is, while gradual, beginning.
The paleness of his face is proof beyond all doubt.
Such statements are recorded by
Entourage-type autoreivs such as myself.
I want you to hear them.
Have you found any trace of PROXY?
Since it is no longer within the city limits,
it would be difficult to conduct a remote
pursuit investigation using existing systems.
Let's take a simple approach.
We'll use a relic that's been hidden in the underground facility.
Confirmed information release mode.
Oh?
You are referring to the ultra-long-distance transportation device
that was used during the Mosk invasion operation, correct?
"In for a penny, in for a pound."
I'll teach you the meaning of this phrase.
Note: Monad, a symbol of God or totality, comes from the Greek
word μονάς which means "one", "single", or "unique".
We had been calling it the Monad PROXY.
"Monad"?
And we seized it from the Mosk dome by force.
When I was assigned to this facility, it already existed.
Why it was kept enclosed here
and why we were not allowed to let it awaken...
I myself do not know the real reasons for that.
However, I do know some things.
First, it is not human
from both a theological and a biological standpoint.
Secondly, we also could not verify that it had a gender.
It is my belief that to Romdeau city,
PROXY is an entity that could be construed as a life force.
So rather than a monster, it's...
Yes.
It certainly seems to be an entity like God.
One could even say
that it is a key to maintaining the field
we need to survive in this desolate world.
Sounds like something from the occult.
But the data has appeared in reality as well.
In addition, look.
The cells that constitute the subject
are immortal cells called amrita cells.
If we can discover their secret,
we...
An entity that could be the key to human survival...
That is PROXY.
But even that has been lost.
Then that means Romdeau is...
Yes.
But we must not forget
the secret only the two of us know.
There is more than one PROXY.
Well done.
I think you just insulted me.
Now then,
I have one thing I'd like to ask you as well.
Where did you learn the word, "PROXY"?
Your fault for leaving your seat.
Re-l...
To tell you the truth, I don't know why I'm so drawn to it.
An empathetic encounter?
That's not all.
When I saw it, something changed.
Until now, my life required neither doubts nor answers.
All I had to do was to carry out the tasks assigned to me.
Even now, I may still be able to go back to that life.
But...
"But"?
But I have encountered it.
And I have seen the outside world.
I can't turn away from the facts after they've been uncovered.
I must admit
it's just like you to say that.
Still, I am the same way.
I want to know the answers.
That is why I'm here.
Daedalus.
It's just the two of us now.
No...
She is an autoreiv.
I am alone again.
Let's go.
It's where Vince was born, right?
Yeah...
What kind of place is it?
Well, it's...
Well, you'll know once you get there.
Re-l!
Iggy!
We're within the facility!
How is this possible?!
Chairman.
It's infected?
By cogito...
Impossible...
They made the cogito virus into a weapon?
I'm their target.
Raul...
The virus' infection mechanism isn't even known, yet...
It means he's willing to go far in order to monopolize it.
He wants to know where PROXY has gone?
The man who knows that answer...
is Vincent Law.
Re-l,
I got a response from a tap I set up in the Security Bureau.
Beginning trace of target.
Re-l!
Re-l!!!
All alone...
What the last remaining human obtained
was simply time to think...
Memories I'm trying to forget yet cannot recall.
There's some sort of hard lump in my head.
Just what that is...
What is within me...
Even if I were to know what they are,
what good would that do me now?
Now,
when I'm all alone...
I will never see her again.
That's why...
I must forget her, but...
I can't forget that face.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
Things that are good,
things that come,
things that move,
things that are sad,
things that are happy,
things that are alone,
meditation  ray of
light
things that are two,
and things that shine.